[{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She was very scared. She was feeling the speed of the space shuttle. she remembered her mom and wanted to meet her very soon.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.25},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0,"probability":0.2265240103006363}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels both excited and nervous as the shuttle is taking off.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.4583333333333333},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9609663486480713}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"like she can do it !","rating":0,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4197462797164917}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She is nervous but trying to be brave","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.39649733901023865}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Nervous, but also excited to be with her mother.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9583333333333334},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9645602703094482}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Anxious but determined, and attempting to remain positive.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5129938721656799}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels scared, brave, and maybe a little nervous.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.25},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5257648229598999}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Nervous and unsettled, though resolved and determined, because she us after all, eleven years old.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5242353081703186}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Afraid and Vulnerable","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.339803010225296}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna felt thrilled and terrified.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.7741103172302246}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She felt nervous, excited and brave all at the same time.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9583333333333334},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9869886040687561}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels scared and nervous (as she is holding onto her P.A.I.R.) to be on the space shuttle, however is also trying to be brave because she wants to see her mom.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.3333333333333333},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.6435394287109375}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"she feels terrified and scared.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.8333333333333334},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5548734664916992}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna felt nervous","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.647643506526947}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She feels quite nervous.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.43676042556762695}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels excited and scared as the shuttle is taking off and it even affects her heart-rate and her temperature.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.5416666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9540585279464722}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels excited and scared as the shuttle is taking off and it even affects her heart-rate and her temperature.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.5416666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9588257670402527}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna felt both excited and terrified as she was taking off into the unknown!! I love how her P.A.I.R. attempts to comfort her with a statistic about successful space missions. She appears to really appreciate this. :)","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.375},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.977566659450531}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels determined, nervous, scared and excited all at the same time.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.2916666666666667},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9799368381500244}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is anxious, nervous, and excited for the shuttle to take off. She is anxious and nervous because she is an 11 old girl on the shuttle it seems alone. It also appears that she has never been off Earth before and to another world. Her companion prog","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.2916666666666667},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9727120399475098}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She feels very nervous.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.44182124733924866}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She is nervous about travelling in the shuttle to go into space.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.43500128388404846}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna felt excited about her trip, but she as also a little nervous.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.875},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9830242991447449}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna was feeling anxious and excited.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9643459916114807}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"nervous but confident","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.39988526701927185}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She seems a little scared or nervous","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4594709873199463}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is anxious as evidenced by an increased heart rate and body temperature. The narrator makes it abundantly clear that she is worried the launch will end in","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.29453372955322266}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"she thinks she is doing that and she will be with her mom","rating":0,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4007517993450165}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She feels nervous.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4184607267379761}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna","rating":0,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0,"probability":0.1688046157360077}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Nervous","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.35717928409576416}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"nervous","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4295240640640259}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"she is excited and scared","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.875},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9456114768981934}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She is excited but scared at the same time.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.875},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9497936367988586}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is nervous about taking off in the shuttle.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.3333333333333333},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4575241804122925}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"As the shuttle takes off, Shiranna feels scared as stated by her P.A.I.R. But I think it's a combination of many emotions including excitement, wariness, and nervousness. As the shuttle takes off, Shiranna feels scared as stated by her P.A.I.R. But I think","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4131714105606079}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is excited but nervous about the trip. She's very aware of her surroundings, and anticipates the launch with using all of her senses. She is thinking also about her mother, and seeks solace from her PAIR, which I infer serves the function of a ted","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.2916666666666667},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9709975123405457}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She feels nervous and anxious.  She seems to be trying to convince herself that all will be okay.  She feels as if she needs to be brave for P.A.I.R but really is trying to convince herself that she is brave.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.8333333333333334},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.7068796157836914}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels excited and yet nervous about the journey she is about to embark.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9651313424110413}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She felt nervous, determined, and excited. In part because she was doing something she had not done before and in part because she wanted to be with her mother. She also seemed determined as she was giving herself a pep talk.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9583333333333334},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9731457829475403}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is both nervous and excited about the shuttle taking off.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.375},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9618324041366577}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"nervous","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.40838685631752014}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels nervous and excited. She is also eager to see her mom.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9411106705665588}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels nervous and excited to begin the journey to visit her mother","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9707320332527161}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Nervous and afraid","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4852179288864136}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna felt both excited and scared as the shuttle was taking off.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.4583333333333333},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9713979363441467}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She feels nervous and scared, terrified even.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.8333333333333334},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.6294234395027161}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"From the reading I can assume that Shiranna is feeling nervous and anxious.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.8333333333333334},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5206575989723206}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Scared","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.43127962946891785}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels nervous, but excited.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9592258930206299}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shirana feels anxious as the shuttle is leaving the station. She seems to be very young at 11 years old but the text implies that she may not be human since she is going to Earth and away from her home. She seems to interpret her age as a sign of her matur","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.8333333333333334},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.6788652539253235}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"scared","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.35018476843833923}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She feels anxious and excited at the same time.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.875},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.973778486251831}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is nervous and scared.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.8333333333333334},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4076876938343048}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Nervous and excited","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9583333333333334},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9582257866859436}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels anxious, nervous and maybe a little scared. You know this because she is giving herself a prep talk before the launch    Also she squeezes her robot for comfort and this robot can sense her increase heart rate and tells her not to be scared.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.25},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.6604728698730469}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna felt nervous as the shuttle began to take off.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.25},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.6631801724433899}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels worried, but excited for the journey ahead.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9615997076034546}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"It appears that she is excited but also frightened at the possibility the shuttle would not make it to its destination.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.875},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.93561190366745}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Scared.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.39531540870666504}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels both thrilled and terrified. She is excited to be leaving Earth for the first time and to be with her mother at her destination. Simultaneously, she is scared or anxious as the shuttle accelerates, as evident by her P.A.I.R.‚Äôs determinatio","rating":1,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.375},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9968531131744385}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She is nervous.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4101138412952423}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is scared and nervous as the space shuttle is taking off.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.4166666666666667},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4222542345523834}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels nervous.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.8333333333333334},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.49486783146858215}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She felt thrilled and terrified.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.7689832448959351}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Nervous, excited, and needing reassurance","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9583333333333334},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9549258351325989}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna appears to feel nervous, yet excited.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.968626856803894}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels nervous and excited.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.7916666666666666},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9673203229904175}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She is both scared and excited. She is scared because she has never done this before, but is excited because she will see her mom and because it is an exciting experience to go into space.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.875},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.8908922672271729}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"nervous","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4276179075241089}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Nervous Apprehensive Apprehensive","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.40877753496170044}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"scared","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.36993643641471863}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels scared and nervous as the shuttle is taking off. Her heart even stops.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.5},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.43643346428871155}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna is feeling scared and nervous.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.25},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.515751302242279}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"d","rating":0,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.4450150728225708}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"anxious","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":0.25},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.41071489453315735}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She's excited, but nervous.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9583333333333334},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9632284641265869}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna feels scared and anxious as the shuttle is taking off.","rating":0.5,"testA":{"score":1,"probability":0.5},"testB":{"score":0.5,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0.5,"probability":0.5118412375450134}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"She is very excited, but to some degree she express some signs of nervousness.","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9384976029396057}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"nervous excited","rating":1,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9583333333333334},"testB":{"score":1,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":1,"probability":0.9578915238380432}},{"question":"How does Shiranna feel as the shuttle is taking off?","answer":"Shiranna","rating":0,"testA":{"score":0,"probability":0.9166666666666666},"testB":{"score":0,"probability":1},"testC":{"score":0,"probability":0.20237836241722107}}]
